// data/quiz.js
const quizData = [
    {
      id: '1',
      title: 'Quiz 1',
      questions: [
        {
          question: "What are greenhouse gases?",
          options: ["CO2", "O2", "N2", "He"],
          correctAnswer: 0,
        },
        {
          question: "What does the greenhouse effect do?",
          options: ["Warms the Earth", "Cools the Earth", "Has no effect", "None of the above"],
          correctAnswer: 0,
        },
        {
          question: "What gas is primarily responsible for climate change?",
          options: ["Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Hydrogen"],
          correctAnswer: 1,
        },
        {
          question: "Which of these is a renewable energy source?",
          options: ["Coal", "Oil", "Wind", "Natural Gas"],
          correctAnswer: 2,
        },
        {
          question: "What is the main effect of deforestation?",
          options: ["Increased biodiversity", "Climate change", "Soil fertility", "Water conservation"],
          correctAnswer: 1,
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: '2',
      title: 'Quiz 2',
      questions: [
        {
          question: "What does the greenhouse effect do?",
          options: ["Warms the Earth", "Cools the Earth", "Has no effect", "None of the above"],
          correctAnswer: 0,
        },
        {
          question: "What gas is primarily responsible for climate change?",
          options: ["Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Hydrogen"],
          correctAnswer: 1,
        },
        {
          question: "Which of these is a renewable energy source?",
          options: ["Coal", "Oil", "Wind", "Natural Gas"],
          correctAnswer: 2,
        },
        {
          question: "What is the main effect of deforestation?",
          options: ["Increased biodiversity", "Climate change", "Soil fertility", "Water conservation"],
          correctAnswer: 1,
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is a non-renewable resource?",
          options: ["Wind", "Solar", "Coal", "Hydro"],
          correctAnswer: 2,
        },
      ],
    },
  ];
  
  export default quizData;
  